Guide to the Cornell University Media Services Photo Section records, 1943-1989.
Cornell University Media Services Photo Section records, 1943-1989.
- Series II. Assignments
  - 1981 Century Farm photos, Sheets #1, 2, 3: Farm scenes of Century farm winners, farm buildings, pastures, cows, sweet corn picking, calves, in Oswego, Saratoga, Rennsalaer, Chatauqua counties, Aug. 1981; 865; 66 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #4: Farm scenes in Chatauqua County, Sept. 1981; 865; 15 (Box 20)
  - Cornell in '81, Annual Meeting of the National Association of County Agricultural Agents, Aug. 1981; 866; 2089 (Box 20)
  - Panorama of Ag. Quad. Also photos of Roberts Hall statue and vines, Sept. 1981; 867; 161 (Box 20)
  - County Fair on Ag. Quad, Sept. 1981; 868; 90 (Box 20)
  - Agronomy Crop Garden on Cornell Plantations. General photos, Sept. 1981; 869; 16 color negs. (Box 20)
  - Career Fair in Mann Library South Reading Room, Oct. 2, 1981; 870; 18 (Box 20)
  - ALS News Photographs; Sheet #1: New Charles Pack Research Professor of forest soils taking sample on Turkey Hill Road--a small forest, Oct. 1981; 871; 25 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #2: Dr. Kinella, Professor of Food Science and students in lab in Stocking Hall, Oct. 1981; 871; 24 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #3: Charles Wilkenson--Director of the Toxicology Institute in lab and Dr. Pechuman--Entomology, with his butterfly collection, Oct. 1981; 871; 32 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #4: Swine barn photos of close-up of baby pig being held, to show how tiny they are and a Durac Boar, Oct. 1981; 871; 20 (Box 20)
  - Sheets #5-7: Cornell Orchard photos showing transporting, sorting, picking and sales in showroom, Oct. 1981; 871; 36, 15 (Box 20)
  - ALS Alumni Round-Up--Stan Warren, Paul Gallagher (Major Speakers) in Bailey Hall, Sept. 1981; 872; 71 (Box 20)
  - Ag. & Tech Colleges Presidents, Deans, and other representatives at a conference in BTI, Sept. 1981; 873; 23 (Box 20)
  - Ag. Extension Brochure Photos, Sheet #1: Jan Gibson & Stanley Monroe in TV Station WSTM in Syracuse, NY, Oct. 1981; 874; 18 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #2: Master Gardeners programs in Syracuse--Green Lakes State Park, Sept. 1981; 874; 35 (Box 20)
  - Sheets #3 & 4: Forestry, Tug Hill, NY & Constableville, NY, Oct. 1981; 874; 46 (Box 20)
  - Sheets #4-6: Robert Howlands Farm in Candor, NY, Oct. 1981; 874; 32, 7 color negs (Box 20)
  - Sheet #7: Lou Getman at her desk in Constableville, NY, Oct. 1981; 874; 6 (Box 20)
  - Dean Call presenting a certificate to Gerber Foods rep./ Gerber Foods rep. presenting certificate to their scholarship (grant) winner, Sept. 1981; 875; 10 (Box 20)
  - Empire Farm Days color photos, Aug. 1981; 876; 12 (Box 20)
  - New agents taken for 1981 orientation., Nov. 1981; 877; 93 (Box 20)
  - Agent Orientation, Nov. 1981; 877; 18 (Box 20)
  - Donor-Recipient reception Trustee-Council Weekend. Taken at West Lounge Statler (Board of Trustees), Nov. 1981; 878; 62 (Box 20)
  - Food service workers hands with variety of different foods. To be used in brochure, Nov. 1981; 879; 102 (Box 20)
  - Transfer Day--Ag. HE, & I & LR. Student panel and prospective transfer students in Schoellkopf Memorial Room, Nov. 1981; 880; 20 (Box 20)
  - Pothole workshop--special machine called "Falling Weight Deflectoneter" taken in parking lot of Sheraton Inn, Ithaca, Nov. 1981; 881; 16 (Box 20)
  - Child Protective Caseworker Training Institution sponsored by HDFS/ Family Life Development Center. Taken at Howard Johnson in Ithaca, NY, Nov. 1981; 882; 20 (Box 20)
  - Emeritus Tea for Dean Ziegler, Oct. 1981; 883; 63 (Box 20)
  - College Council (HE) Orientation in MVR Faculty Lounge, Nov. 1981; 884; 27 (Box 20)
  - HE Forum, Sheet #1: Jogger at Stuart Park (Julie Miller), Nov. 1981; 885; 4 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #2: Elementary students getting on and off school bus at Dryden Elementary (Leon Olds--bus driver), Nov. 1981; 885; 13 (Box 20)
  - "Cornell Classic" livestock Holstein auction, Nov. 1981; 886; 20 (Box 20)
  - Home Study photos--Gloria Pidduck, Bud Hayward, Nancy Campbell, Bob Nolan, Janelle Taver, Gene German, Wendell Earle, Judy Neno, Nov. 1981; 887; 5 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #2: George (Bud) Hayward at his desk in Warren Hall, Dec. 1981; 887; 8 (Box 20)
  - Human Ecology Annual Report, Sheet #1: John Doris and the Family Life Development Staff, Dec. 1981; 888; No. of Negs: (Box 20)
  - Sheet #2: Ed Ostrander in class and viewing slides, Dec. 1981; 888; No. of Negs: (Box 20)
  - Sheet #3 & 4: Clarence Reed counseling student, Dec. 1981; 888; No. of Negs: (Box 20)
  - Sheet #5: Staff sketch of Clarence Reed, Dec. 1981; 888; No. of Negs: (Box 20)
  - Sheet #6 & 14: Sue West and student in conference, Dec. 1981; 888; No. of Negs: (Box 20)
  - Sheet #7& 8: John Mason--International Nutrition portrait at his desk, Dec. 1981; 888; No. of Negs: (Box 20)
  - Sheet #9: Jean-Pierre Habicht office portrait in Savage Hall, Dec. 1981; 888; No. of Negs: (Box 20)
  - Sheet #10: Herbert Engman office portraits in MVR, Dec. 1981; 888; No. of Negs: (Box 20)
  - Sheet #11: Allen Hahn office portraits in MVR, Dec. 1981; 888; No. of Negs: (Box 20)
  - Sheet #12: Mike Johnson--office portrait and at computer terminal, Dec. 1981; 888; No. of Negs: (Box 20)
  - Sheet #13: Ed Ostrander--Office portraits in MVR, Dec. 1981; 888; No. of Negs: (Box 20)
  - Sheet #15: Nevart Yaghlian in her office in MVR; and Lynn Wiley in her office in MVR, Dec. 1981; 888; No. of Negs: (Box 20)
  - Sheet #16: Lynn Wiley in her office in MVR, Dec. 1981; 888; No. of Negs: (Box 20)
  - Sheet #17: Lynn Wiley with student and student ambassador talking with prospective students, Dec. 1981; 888; No. of Negs: (Box 20)
  - Sheet #17 & 18: Fall Creek neighborhood, Dec. 1981; 888; No. of Negs: (Box 20)
  - Sheet #19: Student Housing in Collegetown, Feb. 1981; 888; No. of Negs: (Box 20)
  - Sheet #20: Michael Lea/Assistant Professor/CEH; Jane McGonigal/Senior Extension Associate and Program Coordinator/Cooperative Extension; one 8x10 color transparency of NYS, Feb. 1981; 888; No. of Negs: (Box 20)
  - Sheet #21: Glen Elder in his office in MVR, Dec. 1981; 888; No. of Negs: (Box 20)
  - Mon Cochran Interview with James Titus/Media Services in MVR. To be used for Human Ecology Forum, Jan. 1982; 889; 37 (Box 20)
  - ALS News, Sheet #1: Susan and Karen Draves, ALS '81; in library archives looking up historical documents on the grange, Feb. 1982; 890; 12 (Box 20)
  - Sheets #2 & 3: Career Placement Office with students. Bill Alberta in office and with students (Dir. Of Career Placement), Feb. 1982; 890; No. of Negs: (Box 20)
  - Sheets #4 & 5: William Alberta/Director of Career Placement, Feb. 1982; 890; 8 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #4: Ted Huller/Director of Research, Feb. 1982; 890; 7 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #5: Gereld Hill/Development Officer of Dev. and Alumni Affairs, Feb. 1982; 890; 9 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #6: Lobster Research by Ronald Harris-Warrick and Langmuir Lab, Feb. 1982; 890; 25 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #7: New construction on Animal Science barns behind BTI (Green Barns), Mar. 1982; 890; 16 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #8: Copy of illustration of Academic II, Mar. 1982; 890; 8 (Box 20)
  - HE News, Sheet #1: Louise Ingraham '82 (mature student), Feb. 1982; 891; 4 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #2: Margery Leonard--Audio Visual Aide/Nut. Science and James Forside/Assistant Dr. Admin/HE, Feb. 1982; 891; 9 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #3: James Forside and Shelly White-Means/Assistant Professor CEH, Feb. 1982; 891; 12 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #4: Shelly White-Means and Patricia Pollack/CED, Feb. 1982; 891; 12 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #5: Patricia Pollack and John Ford/Assistant Professor HSS, Feb. 1982; 891; 11 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #6: John Ford and Carolyn Cook/Alumni Dir. HE, Feb. 1982; 891; 12 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #7: Gloria Turner '82 and Simone Clemhout/Associate Professor CEH, Feb. 1982; 891; 12 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #8: Melissa Winter '82 HE Student, Feb. 1982; 891; 9 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #9: Group photo of Rice Family and group photo of Rice Speech Contest finalists, Feb. 1982; 891; 11 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #10: Mary Bloetjes/Emeritus Professor HE Nutrition, Feb. 1982; 891; 12 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #11: Seth Plattus/Human Ecology student, Feb. 1982; 891; 5 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #12: Reception to open new CISER Computer facility in G85, MVR, Mar. 1982; 891; 37 (Box 20)
  - Dr. Warren Knapp and students working with weather tracking equipment on 11th floor Bradfield. Taken for the Ag. Society Show, Dec. 1981; 892; 20 (Box 20)
  - Computer training for faculty (HE & AG), Jan. 1982; 893; 28 (Box 20)
  - Beeswax candles and candle holders with carburetors, Jan. 1982; 894; 23 (Box 20)
  - James Mason and James Titus posing at the home of James Mason to be used in their new book, Fall 1981; 895; 11 (Box 20)
  - Aerial views of Research Park, Lab of Ornithology, North Campus, Cayuga Lake, Ithaca College. Ag. Quad, Fall Creek Falls, Martha Van, Equine Research Park, Oct. 1981; 896; 45 (Box 20)
  - Plotting graphs on a tektronis computer (Gary Buhrmaster), Jan. 1982; 897; 6 (Box 20)
  - Sorting Nestle entry contest forms and deciding on winners (Rod Hawkes, Sharon Cooper, Gene German), Feb. 1982; 898; 16 (Box 20)
  - "Making the Most of the 80's" exhibit, Feb. 1982; 899; 18 (Box 20)
  - Model of the Ag. Quad built by Landscape Arch. Students, Feb. 1982; 900; 9 (Box 20)
  - Second floor MVR lab and third floor hallway and lab on west wing/MVR. Taken to show deterioration of labs and hallways, Feb. 1982; 901; 56 (Box 20)
  - BTI Annual Report Photos, Feb. 1982; 902; 305 (Box 20)
  - Photos of old barn between Fernow and Rice Hall due for demolition, Mar. 1982; 903; 14 (Box 20)
  - Winter campus scenes of Human Ecology and Ag., Feb. 1982; 904; 72 (Box 20)
  - Human Ecology Activities, Sheet #1: Lab Technician in DNS labs on second floor of new wing in MVR (Frames 16-35) Frames 36 & 37 are of a student working in DNS Learning Resource Room, Mar. 1982; 905; 23 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #2: Frames 2-4 are students working in DNS Learning Resource Room. Frames 5-29--Students at computer facility in basement of MVR. Frames 30-37--lab technicians in DNS Research Facility in basement of MVR, Mar. 1982; 905; 37 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #3: Frames 2-5--Design class; Frames 6-28--former HE students return to give seminars about their field of work; Frames 29-6A--Students working in third floor MVR DNS lab, Mar. 1982; 905; 41 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #4: Frames 2-18--Fieldcrest Mills representative interviewing students for a job. Frames 19-37--Peter Forano with Senior Design Class students Chris Woiwide and Laura Older, Mar. 1982; 905; 37 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #5: Students in textile lab at 280 MVR Frames 1-9a; lecture being given at Lakeside Nursing Home by HSS students frames 10a-15a; Research in Nell Mondy's lab--Nut. Sciences Frames 16a-19a (Negs 16a-19a returned to Nell Mondy Mar 22, 1985), Apr. 1982; 905; 19 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #6: HSS students giving Field Study presentation on the effects of salt. Helen Burris and Clarence Reed were present, Apr. 1982; 905; 49 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #7: Counseling--also, studying in Career Library, Apr. 1982; 905; 27 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #8: Simulation--behavior with Bob Babcock in Bailey Hall, Apr. 1982; 905; 15 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #9 & 10: Maternity Clothing Design Critique and Photo Session with Anita Racine in MVR, Apr. 1982; 905; 44 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #11: Minority Admissions Meeting, Apr. 1982; 905; 20 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #12: Brown Bag Seminar which takes place every month in HDFS--James Turner & Phil Schoggen, Apr. 1982; 905; 24 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #13: Apparel Design final presentations and 3-D Design, Apr. 1982; 905; 37 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #14: CEH 111 Class in MVR Amphitheater and HDFS class in Uris Hall, May 1982; 905; 29 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #15: MVR student computer room and portrait of Randy Kirk sitting at computer, May 1982; 905; 11 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #16: Leonard Mankowski's class "Elements of House Design", May 1982; 905; 13 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #17: Nursery School, HE campus scenes and Interior Design II (Paul Eshelman class), May 1982; 905; 36 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #18: DEA 240 class at AM. Comm. Cable Station producing fashion show put on by Apparel Design Class, May 1982; 905; 30 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #19: Interior Design II Class (Paul Eshelman, instructor), May 1982; 905; 22 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #20: Public showing and critique of Apparel Designs, DEA Design 5 Class and Apparel 3 Class, May 1982; 905; 36 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #21: Student Profiles, May 1982; 905; 38 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #22: Group of students in front of MVR, May 1982; 905; 21 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #23: HE Jennifer Hughes, May 1982; 905; 9 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #24: Students in discussion in MVR Faculty Lounge and HE students Elliot Block and Jennifer Hughes portraits, May 1982; 905; 36 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #25: Students using computers in MVR Computer Room with Ed Kain, May 1982; 905; 32 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #26-29: "DNS Field Study Students" working at Wilson Memorial Hospital in Johnson City, NY, July 1982; 905; 128 (Box 20)
  - Milk Marketing Inc. scholarship presentation to Ag. Student Debbie McIntyre. Milk Marketing reps are Cal Henry and Don Schriver with Dean David Call, Mar. 1982; 906; 5 (Box 20)
  - HE News, Sheet #1: Rosemary Adams--Ad. Aide in Field Study HE, Mar. 1982; 907; 12 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #2: Gary Sloan--Assistant Professor DEA, Mar. 1982; 907; 12 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #3: Ann Schruben--HE Grad Student in HSS, Mar. 1982; 907; 11 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #4: Cornell University United Religious Works meeting in Faculty Lounge in MVR, Mar. 1982; 907; 27 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #5: Lorraine Johnson at her desk at Planned Parenthood of Tompkins County, Mar. 1982; 907; 12 (Box 20)
  - Sheets # 6-8: Racism Conference at MVR Faculty Commons, Apr. 1982; 907; 86 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #9: Office portrait of Beverly Surine, Apr. 1982; 907; 11 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #10: Jonathan Plotkin--Grad student in HDFS in Ciser Computer room in MVR, Apr. 1982; 907; 7 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #11-13: Advisory Council meeting, Apr. 1982; 907; 53 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #13 & 14: Portrait of Judy Williams, May 1982; 907; 12 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #15: Candid interview of Joan Brumberg in her office in MVR, May 1982; 907; 25 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #16: Aoi Takeuchi--portrait taken in MVR faculty commons, May 1982; 907; 6 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #17: Kelly Behan--portrait taken in MVR faculty commons, May 1982; 907; 6 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #18: Teaching awards presented at faculty meeting--Marge Devine, Barbara Lust and Dean Ziegler, May 1982; 907; 18 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #19: Liz McCarney and assistant going over video tapes (Elizabeth McCarney is Visiting Fellow for 1981-1982 in HDFS. She is a George Washington Goler Associate Prof. at the University of Rochester Medical Center.), June 1982; 907; 12 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #20: Food Service Update/Dept. Nutritional Sciences, July 1982; 907; 26 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #21: Judith Brown/HE Alumni, July 1982; 907; 18 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #22: Roger Richardson/HE Counselor-Frames 1a-9a and Jan Kennedy Olson--Director of Mann Library with Jeanette McCay (HE Alumni) and Vivian Warters, former Associate Director of Mann Library and former Home Economics Librarian. Frames 10a-20a, Aug. 1982; 907; 26 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #23: Constance Shipiro--Assistant Prof. Human Serv., Aug. 1982; 907; 16 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #24: Diva Sanjur--Professor Nutritional Sciences, Aug. 1982; 907; 10 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #25: Mary Lou Brewer--Program Coord./Coop. Ext., Sept. 1982; 907; 15 (Box 20)
  - Sunburst with deep red filter and photo of Mann Library and Ag. Quad, taken from roof of Roberts Hall, Mar. 1982; 908; 11 (Box 20)
  - NADP Monitoring Station, Aurora, NY, Mar. 1982; 909; 26 (Box 20)
  - Photos of Catherine Cowell teaching and lecturing in MVR, Apr. 1982; 910; 72 (Box 20)
  - American Greetings Corporation scholarship presentation to Richard Rego by Al Stenger rep. of American Greetings Corp., Apr. 1982; 911; 4 (Box 20)
  - Human Ecology Forum, Sheet #1: Corporate Arms/Doug, Marjie, and Amy Albern, Apr. 1982; 912; 13 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #2: Robert Topor/animated stress, Apr. 1982; 912; 12 (Box 20)
  - Countryman class designing and editing the Countryman, Apr. 1982; 913; 14 (Box 20)
  - New agent photos taken for 1982 Agent Orientation, Apr. 1982; 914; 41 (Box 20)
  - Cornell Livestock Show, Apr. 1982; 915; 70 (Box 20)
  - Reception for Jane Goodall with Dean Ziegler, Dr. Neshiem and students in MVR Auditorium, Apr. 1982; 916; 13 (Box 20)
  - Fish Tasting Panel testing for freshness of fish with Joe Reganstein and Donna Kline, Apr. 1982; 917; 25 (Box 20)
  - Speech Finalists--86 Memorial Speech Contest, May 1982; 918; 7 (Box 20)
  - ALS News, Sheets #1 & 2: Jan Olson--office portrait in Mann Library, May 1982; 919; 18 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #3: Dan Sisler speaking to Ag. Business group conference, June 1982; 919; 27 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #4: Agronomy Field Days being held at Mount Pleasant Ag. Research Farm, July 1982; 919; 31 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #5: ALS Grouse counting group (ALS Conservation Group), July 1982; 919; 5 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #6: Clarence Benson farm in Lansing with family, Aug. 1982; 919; 26 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #7: 4-H Congress, Aug. 1982; 919; 12 (Box 20)
  - Sheets #8-10: ALS Round-Up, Aug. 1982; 919; 110 (Box 20)
  - Sheets #11-13: Glen Andrews Farm and Morgan Horses, Aug. 1982; 919; 73 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #14: Joseph Novak/ Prof. Education office photo, Feb. 1982; 919; 5 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #15: Ivanka Maglich/taken at Mann Library, Feb. 1982; 919; 18 (Box 20)
  - Campus Scenes, Sheet #1: HE Campus scenes, Martha's Café; West Door MVR; also dog in front of Caldwell Hall, May 1982; 920; 16 (Box 20)
  - Sheets #2-5: Ag. Quad, Minns Garden, May 1982; 920; 51 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #6: Students in Mann Library, May 1982; 920; 35 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #7: Warren Hall, Aug. 1982; 920; 9 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #8: McGraw Tower, Aug. 1982; 920; 12 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #9: Statue on top of Roberts Hall without stick, Nov. 1982; 920; 12 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #10: Graffiti on walls of Roberts Hall attic-stairway to roof, Spring 1985; 920; 19 (Box 20)
  - Art Pratt and Bob Childs in pepper garden--East Ithaca Plots, May 1982; 921; 26 (Box 20)
  - HE Forum, Sheets #1-3: Portraits of Cathleen Zick, Steve Goggin, Andrea Eggleston, Martha Mapes, Carolyn Smith, June 1982; 922; 66 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #4: Students leaving school and crowd shots of students, June 1982; 922; No. of Negs: (Box 20)
  - Sheet #5 & 6: Adolescent simulating smoking marijuana, June 1982; 922; 8 (Box 20)
  - Sheets #7-9: Teenagers on steps of GIAC and in poolroom playing pool, June 1982; 922; 40 (Box 20)
  - Sheets #10 & 11: Youngsters ages 8 thru 12 playing on GIAC playground, June 1982; 922; 57 (Box 20)
  - Sheet # 12: Youngsters ages 8 thru 12 sitting on GIAC steps, June 1982; 922; 12 (Box 20)
  - Sheet#13: Teenagers holding hands at Stewart Park (Ann Calvert and Philip Brown), June 1982; 922; 13 (Box 20)
  - Sheet #14: Dr. Zilversmit & Grad student of Nut. Sciences doing research/autopsy of rabbit and Dr. Zilversmit & associate at computer, Sept. 1982; 922; 37 (Box 20)
  - Cornell University Commencement, May 1982; 923; 142 (Box 20)
  - Senior Barbeque in Livestock Pavilion, May 1982; 924; 78 (Box 20)
  - TITLE, DATE; Job #; NO. of Negs. (Box BOX)
  - Ithaca Commons, June 1982; 925; 36 (Box 21)
  - Girls using 4-H butterfly catching kit (Ann Calvert and Laura Calvert), May 1982; 926; 37 (Box 21)
  - Highway School, June 1982; 927; 16 (Box 21)
  - Tree Dedication Ceremony, June 1982; 928; 50 (Box 21)
  - Ag. Alumni Breakfast, June 1982; 929; 80 (Box 21)
  - HE Alumni Breakfast, June 1982; 930; 64 (Box 21)
  - 4-H kids using trapper kit with Gary Goff. The kids are Keith Armstrong, Scott and Jody Oaks (blonds), June 1982; 931; 36 (Box 21)
  - Sheets #1-3: Parent and teacher in school setting with child at Central Elementary School, June 1982; 932; 61 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #4: School children waiting for and getting on school bus, June 1982; 932; 14 (Box 21)
  - Mayor Koch visiting Benson Farm in Lansing, Experimental Fields by Cornell Seed Cooperative and the NYS Vet. College, July 1982; 933; 133 (Box 21)
  - Plant Breeding Synopsis and Golden Age of Corn Genetics, July 1982; 934; 94 (Box 21)
  - Northeast American Society of Agronomy, July 1982; 935; 6 (Box 21)
  - Baker Institute Activities, Aug. 1982; 936; 199 (Box 21)
  - BTI Activities, Aug. 1982; 937; 43 (Box 21)
  - Fallen tree near Mt. Pleasant Research Farm. Example of hardpan soil, Aug. 1982; 938; 10 (Box 21)
  - Candid pictures of dedication of the Baker Farm to Cornell. Scenic photos of the Bakers Willsbora Farm. Dean Dave Call, Provost Kennedy and faculty with Mr. E. Veraland Baker and Mr. Henry Uihlein, Aug. 1982; 939; 166, 38 color neg (Box 21)
  - Lew Lehrman (Republican Candidate for Governor) visits Empire Farm Days (Dean Call and others), Aug. 1982; 940; 77 (Box 21)
  - Dr. Ed Raffensperger with students Lynn Sweet, Brian Dratch, Terry Smith and Paul Orioli on Ag. Quad, Aug. 1982; 941; 28 (Box 21)
  - Overall photos of BTI Research Field; aerials of Cornell Campus, Aug. 1982; 942; 52 (Box 21)
  - Cooperative Extension Advisory Meeting, Sept. 1982; 943; 41 (Box 21)
  - Century Farms/1982, Aug./Sept. 1982; 944; 91 (Box 21)
  - Cozy Windows Class in Cooperative Extension Bldg, Ithaca, NY, Nov. 1982; 945; 19 (Box 21)
  - Trustee-Council Scholarship Donor Recipient Reception, Oct. 22, 1982; 946; 42 (Box 21)
  - New Agents Orientation 1982/1983--Sheet #2--Kathy Giacomi--Steuban Co. Coop., Nov. 1982; 947; 141 (Box 21)
  - Harold Sweet checking weeds at Guterman Lab, Nov. 1982; 948; 22 (Box 21)
  - Media Services Photo Section Staff Photos, Nov. 1982; 949; 27 (Box 21)
  - Human Ecology News, Sheet #1: Portrait of two student workers in Carolyn Cooks office in MVR, Nov. 1982; 950; 12 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #2: Portraits of Susan Sayer, HE Student, Nov. 1982; 950; 9 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #3: Portraits of Ethel Sampson, Nov. 1982; 950; 10 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #4: Portraits of Phyllis Stout--Frames 2-10 and Peter Zorn, Frames 11-19, Nov. 1982; 950; 18 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #5: Emeritus Professors Tea in Faculty Commons in MVR, Nov. 1982; 950; 27 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #6: Peter Schwartz, Asst. Prof. DEA, Nov. 1982; 950; 8 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #7: David Caruso, graduate student in HDFS, Nov. 1982; 950; 6 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #7: Nicholas Markovich, Assistant Prof. DEA, Nov. 1982; 950; 6 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #8: Andrea Eggleston lecturing students (neg. destroyed), Nov. 1982; 950; 1 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #9: Microwave Research with Gertrude Armbruster and wall mural in MVR, Dec. 1982; 950; 25 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #10: HE grad student/Tony Sciano, Feb. 1982; 950; 16 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #11: Marion Potts--HDFS Frames 1-21A; Simone Clemhout CEH, frames 31-37, Feb. 1982; 950; 28 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #12: Office portraits and candids in Faculty Commons. Polly Spending-Frames 4a-12; Michael Basseches--Frames 13a-17a; Elsie Van Buren Rice Award Candids, Feb. 1982; 950; 20 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #13: Visiting lecturer Allen Sanders in Nut. Sciences (S. Kumanyika), Apr. 1983; 950; 21 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #14: Field Study Reception/S. Kumanyika-DNS, Apr. 1983; 950; 37 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #15: Frames 9-20a: Field Study Reception, Apr. 1983; 950; 12 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #15: Frames 0a-8a: Beth Ziegart's DEA class designing clothing for the "Hotel Ezra Cornell", Apr. 1983; 950; 9 (Box 21)
  - Sheets #16-18: Beth Ziegart's DEA class designing clothing for the "Hotel Ezra Cornell", Apr. 1983; 950; 57 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #19: The Career Fair with Mary Beth Ostman, Apr. 1983; 950; 36 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #20: Tompkins Community Hospital pediatric unit, May 1983; 950; 11 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #21: Dean Jerome Ziegler in his office in MVR, June 1983; 950; 36 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #22: Human Ecology Alumni Breakfast, June 1983; 950; 37 (Box 21)
  - Sheet #23: Andrea Hunter/Grad Student-HE, Frames 6-17; Martha Stipanuk/Asst. Professor Nut. Sci., Frames 18-20a, Aug. 1983; 950; 16 (Box 21)